https://www.dollhouseminiatures.net/index.php?main_page=privacy

Shop for Miniatures
Shop by Product CategoryShop by RoomArtist MiniaturesDollhouse and Room Box KitsGift CertificatesLatest ArrivalsAntique Victorian Die Cut ScrapsSpecial OrderAll Products ...
What's New
Hand Crafted Lavender Velvet Christmas Stocking$3.49
Specials
Handcrafted Melting Cherry Ice Pop$2.95  $2.49
Search
Advanced Search
Who's Online
Right now there are 166 collectors viewing our minis.
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
OUR PRIVACY POLICY HAS NOT CHANGED! We do not now, or have we ever, shared your personal information with any third party.
Mainly Minis Dollhouse Miniatures takes your privacy as seriously as you do. To help ensure your privacy, we use encryption technology to keep your personal information as secure as possible. This includes your billing, credit card, and account information; none of this can be read as it travels to our system.
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise share your personal information, such as name, email address, physical address, phone numbers, buying history, etc. You do not have to worry about receiving unsolicited email from other companies or individuals as a result of shopping at Mainly Minis
In order to make shopping and shipping easier, you need to complete our registration process, which includes setting up a unique Username and Password. To modify your personal information, you will need to click on "MY ACCOUNT", and enter your user name and password. If you have any questions regarding our privacy practices, please contact us.
Free Shipping!
Artists
Please Select
Alice Zinn
All Through The..
Angie Scarr
BA Miniatures
Barbara Kummero..
Bella
Bespaq
Bodo Hennig
Bonnie White Wa..
Brooke Tucker
Carolyn McVicke..
Carolyn's Creat..
Christmas Trees..
Cinderella
D Design
Devine Miniatur..
Hudson River Mi..
Itsy Bitsy Mini
Jacob Wenzel
Jacqueline's
Jason Getzan
Jeannetta Kenda..
Jim Pounder
LAB Miniature D..
Lola Originals
Lorraine M Hell..
Lucy Iducovich
Lynn O'Shaughne..
Margene
Marie's Minis
Marilyn Crocket..
Mary Kinloch
Matthias Matthe..
Michael Mortime..
Michelle of Aus..
Miniature Displ..
Miniature Porce..
Minis by Gloria
Montserrat Folc..
Mr Ks Neon
Nantasy Fantasy
Ni-Glo Lamps
Paintings by C...
Peter Acquisto
Phil Grenyer Gl..
Prestige Leathe..
Reutter Porcela..
Royal Tunbridge..
Sam Dunlap
Shadow Box
Sir Thomas Thum..
Small Creations
Steve Klein
T Wolfert
Taller Targioni
Tanuki & Rosebu..
Taylor Jade
The Dolls Cobbl..
Tucker's Tiny T..
Virginia Anders..
Warren Richards..
Wesley K Whitma..
Wilhelmina Mini..
World of Mini B..
We Accept
Personal ChecksGladly Accepted
The products on this site are collectible miniatures for adults and are not meant for children
Quick LinksHomeFeatured ProductsSpecialsWhat's NewAll Products ...
InformationAbout UsSite MapGift Certificate FAQDiscount CouponsNewsletter Unsubscribe
Customer ServiceContact UsShipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseMy Account
All photographs, artwork, images, descriptions and color schemes
are the exclusive copyright of Mainly Minis Incand may not be used without prior permission.
Mainly Minis, mainly.minis!, Mainly Minis Dollhouse Miniatures and dollhouseminiatures.net are Trademarks of Mainly Minis, Inc.
